replacemyself.com 2010-12-29

# Replace Myself | Privacy Policy

#### ReplaceMyself.com Privacy Statement

The basic gist of this is that we won't sell or rent your private info. We care about your privacy. We hate spam, too. 

When you use this website, you consent to the use of your personal information by ReplaceMyself.com in the manner specified in this Privacy Statement.

#### Personal Information

We require customers who register to use the services offered on our website to give us personally identifiable information such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, institution affiliation, credit card number, checking account number, or date of birth. This personal information is collected and used by ReplaceMyself.com for the purpose of facilitating a relationship or business transaction. We will not sell, trade or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties.

#### Private Information

For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on our servers. Our payment gateway provider, (ModularMerchant.com and Authorize.net), keeps this information encrypted and secure on your behalf. 

#### E-mail

ReplaceMyself.com does not sell or rent e-mail addresses to anyone. ReplaceMyself.com may generate e-mail for the following types of communication:

1\. Notification e-mail to which the individual may subscribe and unsubscribe.

2\. Transactional e-mail, which is the result of a business transaction initiated with ReplaceMyself.com.

3\. Relationship e-mail, which is sent as an informational service because of a relationship with ReplaceMyself.com.

4\. Commercial e-mail, which is sent to promote an ReplaceMyself.com product or service; you may opt to not receive this type of e-mail.

5\. Correspondence from ReplaceMyself.com as a result of a communication initiated by a member or customer.

E-mail that has a provision for opt-out will include instructions on how to do so. All inquiries regarding subscription-based e-mails should be directed to ReplaceMyself.com Customer Service (see Contact Information below).

ReplaceMyself.com may occasionally send informational or promotional materials to members and customers. You may choose to exclude yourself from all, none, or only non-ReplaceMyself.com mailings by contacting Customer Service (see Contact Information below).

#### Non-personal Information

We may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include:  
* IP address of computer  
* Browser-related information  
* Locations visited on the website  
* HTTP cookies.

ReplaceMyself.com may use this information to help us in website research and development or to facilitate restricted website services.

#### IP Address

IP addresses are used to verify access rights of licensed subscribers to ReplaceMyself.com products or services that require license agreements. They also aid in the general administration of the website.

#### HTTP Cookies

A HTTP Cookie is a piece of data that is stored by your browser in either your computer's memory or on your computer's hard drive. ReplaceMyself.com uses cookies to keep track of user session identity on the website, such as tracking items in a shopping cart or maintaining access to restricted website services via ReplaceMyself.com Service Account. Cookies are also used to track the effectiveness of various services provided on ReplaceMyself.com website. Browsers generally allow you to disable cookies. Services on ReplaceMyself.com website that require a login to an ReplaceMyself.com Service Account require that cookies are enabled.

#### Monitoring, Enforcement and Legal Requests

ReplaceMyself.com has no obligation to monitor the website or the use of the website, or to retain the content of any user session. However, ReplaceMyself.com reserves the right at all times to monitor, review, retain and/or disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request or to cooperate with law enforcement and other authorities in investigating a claim of illegal activity. We may use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to protect our service, website, customers or others. 

#### Third-Parties

ReplaceMyself.com uses third-party intermediaries for several business purposes, including credit card validation, data gathering, and other services. These third-parties are permitted to use your personal information only to provide ReplaceMyself.com with a specific service and not for any other purpose. Please contact ReplaceMyself.com Customer Service (see ReplaceMyself.com Contact Information below) if you believe this policy has been violated.

#### Other Sites

This Privacy Statement only addresses ReplaceMyself.com use and disclosure of the information we collect from you. The ReplaceMyself.com website may contain links to other websites. ReplaceMyself.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other websites. To the extent that you visit or disclose personal information to other websites, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of these other websites. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose any personal information.

#### Transmission Errors or Unauthorized Acts

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, ReplaceMyself.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or any information provided by our online services, and you do so at your own risk. ReplaceMyself.com will not be liable for disclosures of your personal information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. However, once we receive your transmission, we do our best to ensure its security on our systems by making reasonable efforts to protect the information. 

#### Security

Any information provided to ReplaceMyself.com is treated with care and discretion. ReplaceMyself.com will take a proactive approach to ensure the information is kept private and not misused. 

#### Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this website, your dealings with the website, or would like to provide comments, you can contact ReplaceMyself.com Customer Services by e-mail at support@ReplaceMyself.com, or by regular mail to: 

ReplaceMyself  
770 E Main St. #250   
Lehi, UT 84043 

This Privacy Statement is subject to change at any time, so please check back from time to time.
